Register of the Poland. Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych Records, 1919-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- SERIES NO. 647. TURKEY, ANKARA, EMBASSY
  - 1944
    - Documentation of accounts
      - February (Folder 12)
      - March (Folder 13)
      - April (Box 455, Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Folder 9)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 10)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 11)
    - Military mission (Folder 12)
- SERIES NO. 648. TURKEY, ISTANBUL, CONSULATE GENERAL
  - 1940
    - General (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - Military mission (Folder 2)
    - Personal files (Folder 3)
  - 1941
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Audit (Folder 5)
    - Budget (Folder 6)
    - Military mission (Folder 7)
    - Personal files (Folder 8)
    - Transport (Folder 9)
  - 1941-1942. Inventory and final report by Alfred Poninski (Folder 10)
  - 1942
    - Audit
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Enclosures (Folder 12)
    - Budget (Folder 13)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 14)
      - February (Folder 15)
      - March (Folder 16)
      - April (Folder 17)
      - May (Folder 18)
      - June (Folder 19)
      - July (Folder 20)
      - August (Folder 21)
      - September (Folder 22)
      - October (Folder 23)
      - November (Box 457, Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan-June (Folder 3)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 4)
    - Personal files (Folder 5)
    - Transport (Folder 6)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Audit
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Enclosures (Folder 9)
    - Budget (Folder 10)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 11)
      - February (Folder 12)
      - March (Folder 13)
      - April (Folder 14)
      - May (Folder 15)
      - June (Folder 16)
      - July (Folder 17)
      - August (Folder 18)
      - September (Box 458, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 5)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 6)
    - Personal files (Folder 7)
  - 1944
    - Audit (Folder 8)
    - Budget (Folder 9)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February (Folder 11)
      - March (Folder 12)
      - April (Folder 13)
      - May (Folder 14)
      - June (Folder 15)
      - July (Box 459, Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 5)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 6)
    - Personal files (Folder 7)
- SERIES NO. 649. HUNGARY, BUDAPEST, LEGATION.
  Closing of operations
  - 1940 (Folder 8)
  - 1941 (Folder 9)
- SERIES NO. 651. GREAT BRITAIN, LONDON, EMBASSY
  - 1940
    - Budget (Folder 10)
    - Personal files (Folder 11)
  - 1941
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Audit (Folder 13)
    - Budget (Folder 14)
    - Embassy archives (Folder 15)
    - Personal files (Folder 16)
    - 1942 (Box 460)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Audit (Folder 2)
    - Budget (Folder 3)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May (Folder 8)
      - June (Folder 9)
      - July
        - Part 1 (Folder 10)
        - Part 2 (Folder 11)
      - August (Box 461, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 6)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 7)
    - Military attache (Folder 8)
    - Personal files (Folder 9)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Audit (Folder 11)
    - Budget (Folder 12)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 13)
      - February (Folder 14)
      - March (Box 462, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
      - December (Folder 10)
    - Ledgers (Box 463)
      - Jan.-June (Folder 1)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 2)
    - Military attache (Folder 3)
    - Personal files (Folder 4)
    - Supplementary family payments (Folder 5)
  - 1944
    - Audit (Folder 6)
    - Budget (Folder 7)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Folder 11)
      - May (Folder 12)
      - June (Box 464, Folder 1)
      - July (Folder 2)
      - August (Folder 3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October (Folder 5)
      - November (Folder 6)
      - December (Folder 7)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 8)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 9)
    - Military attache (Folder 10)
    - Personal files (Folder 11)
- SERIES NO. 652. GREAT BRITAIN, LONDON, CONSULATE
  - 1940
    - General (Box 465, Folder 1)
    - Budget (Folder 2)
  - 1940-1941. Personal files (Folder 3)
  - 1941
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Budget (Folder 5)
  - 1942
    - Audit (Folder 6)
    - Budget (Folder 7)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Folder 11)
      - May (Folder 12)
      - June (Box 466, Folder 1)
      - July (Folder 2)
      - August (Folder 3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October
        - Part 1 (Folder 5)
        - Part 2 (Folder 6)
      - November
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - December (Box 467)
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
    - Inheritance issues (Folder 3)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 4)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 5)
    - Military draft (Folder 6)
    - Parcel recipients in Poland (Folder 7)
    - Personal files (Folder 8)
  - 1943
    - Audit (Folder 9)
    - Budget (Folder 10)
    - Deposit protocols
      - October (Folder 11)
      - November (Folder 12)
      - December (Folder 13)
    - Documentation of accounts (Box 468)
      - January
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
      - February
        - Part 1 (Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Folder 4)
      - March
        - Part 1 (Folder 5)
        - Part 2 (Folder 6)
      - April
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - May
        - Part 1 (Folder 9)
        - Part 2 (Folder 10)
      - June
        - Part 1 (Folder 11)
        - Part 2 (Folder 12)
      - July (Box 469)
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
      - August
        - Part 1 (Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Folder 4)
      - September
        - Part 1 (Folder 5)
        - Part 2 (Folder 6)
      - October
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - November
        - Part 1 (Folder 9)
        - Part 2 (Folder 10)
      - December (Box 470)
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-March (Folder 3)
      - Apr.-June (Folder 4)
      - July-Sept. (Folder 5)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Folder 6)
    - Personal files (Folder 7)
  - 1944
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Audit (Folder 9)
    - Budget (Folder 10)
    - Deposit protocols
      - January
        - Part 1 (Folder 11)
        - Part 2 (Folder 12)
      - February (Folder 13)
      - March (Folder 14)
      - April (Folder 15)
      - May (Box 471, Folder 1)
      - June
        - Part 1 (Folder 2)
        - Part 2 (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
      - December (Folder 10)
    - Documentation of accounts (Box 472)
      - January
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
      - February
        - Part 1 (Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Folder 4)
      - March
        - Part 1 (Folder 5)
        - Part 2 (Folder 6)
      - April
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - May
        - Part 1 (Folder 9)
        - Part 2 (Folder 10)
      - June (Box 473)
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
      - July
        - Part 1 (Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Folder 4)
      - August
        - Part 1 (Folder 5)
        - Part 2 (Folder 6)
      - September
        - Part 1 (Folder 7)
        - Part 2 (Folder 8)
      - October
        - Part 1 (Folder 9)
        - Part 2 (Folder 10)
      - November (Box 474)
        - Part 1 (Folder 1)
        - Part 2 (Folder 2)
      - December
        - Part 1 (Folder 3)
        - Part 2 (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-March (Folder 5)
      - Apr.-June (Folder 6)
      - July-Sept. (Folder 7)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Folder 8)
    - Personal files (Folder 9)
- SERIES NO.652a. GREAT BRITAIN. LONDON. DIPLOMATIC REPRESENTATIONS BY THE ALLIED GOVERNMENTS.
  Documentation of accounts
  - 1942
    - January (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 2)
    - March (Folder 3)
    - April (Folder 4)
    - May (Folder 5)
    - June (Folder 6)
    - July (Folder 7)
    - August (Folder 8)
    - September (Folder 9)
    - October (Folder 10)
    - November (Folder 11)
    - December (Folder 12)
  - 1943
    - January (Folder 13)
    - February (Folder 14)
    - March (Folder 15)
    - April (Folder 16)
    - May (Folder 17)
    - June (Folder 18)
    - July (Folder 19)
    - August (Folder 20)
    - September (Folder 21)
    - October (Folder 22)
    - November (Folder 23)
    - December (Folder 24)
    - 1944 (Box 476)
    - January (Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 2)
    - March (Folder 3)
    - April (Folder 4)
    - May (Folder 5)
    - June (Folder 6)
    - July (Folder 7)
    - August (Folder 8)
    - September (Folder 9)
- SERIES NO. 653. SOVIET UNION, MOSCOW, EMBASSY
  - 1941
    - Administrative and security issues (Folder 10)
    - Evacuation to Kuibyshev (Folder 11)
    - Documentation of accounts, August-December (Folder 12)
    - Personal files
      - Individual files
        - B-O (Folder 13)
        - P-Z (Folder 14)
      - Staff
        - List (Folder 15)
        - Recruitment (Folder 16)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 17)
    - Administrative issues (Folder 18)
    - Budget
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Jan.-June (Folder 20)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 21)
    - Deputies (Folder 22)
    - Documentation of accounts (Box 477)
      - January (Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Folder 8)
      - September (Folder 9)
      - October (Folder 10)
      - November (Folder 11)
      - December (Folder 12)
    - List of staff and salaries (Folder 13)
    - Military misssion (Folder 14)
    - Payroll as of July 1 (Folder 15)
    - Personal files
      - Groups (Folder 16)
      - Individuals (Folder 17)
      - Work contracts (Folder 18)
    - Social welfare (Folder 19)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 20)
    - Audit (Folder 21)
    - Budget
      - General (Folder 22)
      - Preliminary for 1943 (Folder 23)
    - Closing operations (Folder 24)
    - Cultural attache, Instructions for (Folder 25)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 26)
      - February (Folder 27)
      - March (Folder 28)
      - April-May 12 (Folder 29)
      - May 12-June 30 (Folder 30)
      - July (Folder 31)
      - August (Folder 32)
      - September (Folder 33)
      - October (Folder 34)
      - November (Folder 35)
      - December (Folder 36)
    - Embassy's organization (Box 478)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Charts (Folder 2)
    - Financial reports
      - Activities as of January 1, 1943
        - Volume 1 (Folder 3)
        - Volume 2 (Folder 4)
      - "Sprawozdania z dzialalnosci finansowej Ambasady Rzeczypospolitej Polskiej w Z.S.S.R, 7 VIII 1941-12 V 1943" (Folder 5)
    - Individuals designated for medals (Folder 6)
    - Inventories of goods left behind (Folder 7)
    - Ledgers
      - January (Folder 8)
      - April-July (Folder 9)
      - September-December (Folder 10)
    - List of ordered goods (Folder 11)
    - Military mission (Folder 12)
    - Money transfer (Folder 13)
    - Payroll (Folder 14)
    - Personal files (Folder 15)
    - Property rental
      - General (Folder 16)
      - Contract for Teheran premises (Folder 17)
    - Romer, Tadeusz. Appointment as ambassador (Folder 18)
    - Salaries (Folder 19)
    - Severance payments (Folder 20)
    - Social Welfare Department, Archives of (Folder 21)
    - Transfers to other diplomatic posts (Folder 22)
  - 1943-1944. Money transfer (Folder 23)
  - 1944
    - Audit (Folder 24)
    - Food delivery (Folder 25)
    - Personal files (Folder 26)
    - Property rental (Folder 27)
- SERIES NO. 660. LEAGUE OF NATIONS, GENEVA, DELEGATION
  - 1940
    - Documentation of accounts
      - August (Box 479, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - Ledgers, Aug.-Dec. (Folder 6)
  - 1941
    - Budget (Folder 7)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Folder 11)
      - May (Folder 12)
      - June (Folder 13)
      - July (Folder 14)
      - August (Folder 15)
      - September (Folder 16)
      - October (Folder 17)
      - November (Folder 18)
      - December (Folder 19)
    - Ledgers (Box 480)
      - Jan.-June (Folder 1)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 2)
  - 1942
    - Budget (Folder 3)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May (Folder 8)
      - June (Folder 9)
      - July (Folder 10)
      - August (Folder 11)
      - September (Folder 12)
      - October (Folder 13)
      - November (Folder 14)
      - December (Folder 15)
    - Ledgers (Box 481)
      - Jan.-June (Folder 1)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 2)
  - 1943
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February (Folder 4)
      - March (Folder 5)
      - April (Folder 6)
      - May (Folder 7)
      - June (Folder 8)
      - July (Folder 9)
      - August (Folder 10)
      - September (Folder 11)
      - October (Folder 12)
      - November (Folder 13)
      - December (Folder 14)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 15)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 16)
  - 1944
    - Budget (Folder 17)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 18)
      - February (Folder 19)
      - March (Folder 20)
      - April (Folder 21)
      - May (Folder 22)
      - June (Folder 23)
      - July (Box 482, Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 7)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 8)
- SERIES NO. 661. BRITISH INDIA, BOMBAY, CONSULATE
  - 1939-1942. Audit (Folder 9)
  - 1940
    - Audit (Folder 10)
    - Budget (Folder 11)
  - 1940-1944. Deposits (Folder 12)
  - 1941
    - Audit (Folder 13)
    - Budget (Folder 14)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Audit (Folder 16)
    - Budget (Folder 17)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 18)
      - February (Box 483, Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 4)
      - June (Folder 5)
      - July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Box 484, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 5)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 6)
    - Personal files (Folder 7)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Audit (Folder 9)
    - Budget (Folder 10)
    - Costs of telegrams (Folder 11)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 12)
      - February (Folder 13)
      - March (Box 485, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Box 486, Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 3)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 4)
    - Personal files (Folder 5)
    - Poninski, Alfred, Ambassador. Report on his February trip to Bombay (Folder 6)
  - 1944
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Audit (Folder 8)
    - Budget (Folder 9)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February (Box 487, Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 4)
      - June (Folder 5)
      - July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Box 488, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 5)
      - July-Dec. (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Non-budgetary funds for 1939-1942 (Folder 2)
    - Personal files (Folder 3)
- SERIES NO. 662. CANADA, OTTAWA, CONSULATE GENERAL
  - 1939. Ledgers, Aug.-Nov. (Folder 4)
  - 1940
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Budget (Folder 6)
  - 1940-1941. Audit (Folder 7)
  - 1941. Budget (Folder 8)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Audit (Folder 10)
    - Budget (Folder 11)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 12)
      - February (Folder 13)
      - March (Folder 14)
      - April (Folder 15)
      - May (Folder 16)
      - June (Folder 17)
      - July (Box 490, Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - Ledgers, January-December (Folder 7)
    - Military attache (Folder 8)
    - Salaries (Folder 9)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Administrative issues (Folder 11)
    - Audit (Folder 12)
    - Budget (Folder 13)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 14)
      - February (Folder 15)
      - March (Folder 16)
      - April (Folder 17)
      - May (Folder 18)
      - June (Folder 19)
      - July (Box 491, Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 7)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 8)
    - Military attache
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Jan.-Apr. (Folder 10)
      - Aug.-Dec. (Folder 11)
    - Personal files
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Individual (Folder 13)
      - Harajewicz, Henryk (Folder 14)
      - Wegnerowicz, Roman (Folder 15)
    - Salaries (Folder 16)
  - 1944
    - Audit (Folder 17)
    - Budget (Folder 18)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 19)
      - February (Folder 20)
      - March (Folder 21)
      - April (Box 492, Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Folder 9)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-July (Folder 10)
      - Aug.-Dec. (Folder 11)
    - Military attache (Folder 12)
    - Personal files (Folder 13)
    - Propaganda
      - General (Folder 14)
      - Paper for printing of propaganda materials (Folder 15)
- SERIES NO. 664. SOUTH AFRICA, CAPE TOWN, CONSULATE GENERAL
  - 1940
    - General (Box 493, Folder 1)
    - Johannesburg Consular Agency (Folder 2)
  - 1941
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Budget (Folder 4)
    - Johannesburg Consular Agency (Folder 5)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Audit (Folder 7)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Folder 11)
      - May (Folder 12)
      - June (Folder 13)
      - July (Folder 14)
      - August (Folder 15)
      - September (Folder 16)
      - October (Folder 17)
      - November (Folder 18)
      - December (Folder 19)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan-June (Folder 20)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 21)
  - 1943
    - Audit (Folder 22)
    - Budget (Folder 23)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 24)
      - February (Folder 25)
      - March (Box 494, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
      - December (Folder 10)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 11)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 12)
    - Personal files
      - General (Folder 13)
      - Kawalec, Jan (Folder 14)
  - 1944
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Audit (Folder 16)
    - Budget (Folder 17)
    - Documentation of accounts (Box 495)
      - January (Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Folder 8)
      - September (Folder 9)
      - October (Folder 10)
      - November (Folder 11)
      - December (Folder 12)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan-June (Folder 13)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 14)
    - Personal files (Folder 15)
- SERIES NO. 664a. SOUTH AFRICA, JOHANNESBURG, CONSULATE
  - 1941-1942. Audit (Box 496, Folder 1)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Audit (Folder 3)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 4)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Folder 5)
      - May-June (Folder 6)
      - July-Aug. (Folder 7)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Folder 8)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 9)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Audit (Folder 11)
    - Budget (Folder 12)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 13)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Folder 14)
      - May-June (Folder 15)
      - July-Aug. (Folder 16)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Folder 17)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 18)
    - Ledgers, Aug.-Dec. (Folder 19)
    - Personal files (Folder 20)
  - 1944 (Box 497)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Audit (Folder 2)
    - Budget (Folder 3)
    - Personal files (Folder 4)
- SERIES NO. 664b. SOUTH AFRICA, PRETORIA, CONSULATE
  - 1940-1941. Audit (Folder 5)
  - 1942
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Audit (Folder 7)
    - Budget (Folder 8)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 9)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Folder 10)
      - May-June (Folder 11)
      - July-Aug. (Folder 12)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Folder 13)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 14)
  - 1943
    - Audit (Folder 15)
    - Budget (Folder 16)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 17)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Folder 18)
      - May-June (Folder 19)
      - July-Aug. (Folder 20)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Folder 21)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 22)
  - 1944
    - Audit (Folder 23)
    - Budget (Folder 24)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - Jan.-Feb. (Folder 25)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Folder 26)
      - May-June (Folder 27)
      - July-Aug. (Folder 28)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Folder 29)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Folder 30)
- SERIES NO. 665. RHODESIA, LUSACA, CONSULATE
  - 1940
    - Budget (Box 498, Folder 1)
    - Cyprus evacuation. See also SERIES NO. 738/Romania (Folder 2)
  - 1941
    - Audit (Folder 3)
    - Budget (Folder 4)
    - Cyprus evacuation (Folder 5)
  - 1942
    - Audit (Folder 6)
    - Budget (Folder 7)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Folder 11)
      - May (Folder 12)
      - June (Folder 13)
      - July (Folder 14)
      - August (Folder 15)
      - September (Box 499, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - Ledgers
      - Jan.-June (Folder 5)
      - July-Dec. (Folder 6)
    - Personal files (Folder 7)
    - Reorganization of consular services (Folder 8)
  - 1943
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Audit (Folder 10)
    - Budget (Folder 11)
    - Documentation of accounts
      - January (Folder 12)
      - February (Folder 13)
      - March (Folder 14)
      - April (Folder 15)
      - May (Folder 16)
      - July (Folder 17)
      - August (Folder 18)